[panting]
♪
[BAEK]
These are...
But how did they get here?
♪
[ants buzzing]
[whooshes]
[whacks]
[ants chirping]
[growls]
[blasts]
[fire roaring]
♪
It doesn't make sense.
Uh?
[gasps]
That's impossible.
Isn't it?
How did he get in here?
[wind whooshing]
♪
[LEE]
Mister Song.
This means,
they had to shut
the broadcast down
for something, right?
Hm.
But why?
What's happening over there?
♪
It's no good.
Too much confusion
at the scene.
There must be a way
to confirm their status.
Gather all the intel we can.
[JINCHUL]
Yes, sir.
[telephone ringing]
[STAFF 24A]
Director!
So many viewers
are calling in at once
that it's crashing
the phone system!
They're demanding
we resume the broadcast!
And we would if we could!
But in case
you haven't noticed,
we lost contact,
so there's nothing to show!
[grunts]
Besides, what do we do
if all the S-ranks
are already dead?
-[indistinct chatter]
-[angry grunt]
Hey!
What's going on?
We need an update, right now!
-Are you still alive out there?
-Damn it!
My camera quit working!
Of all the times?
Iron!
[roaring]
[wind gusting]
♪
[JINWOO]
Go.
[sword clanking]
[growls]
[electricity crackling]
[DONGWOOK]
I'm not following any of this.
Who are these shadows?
And how did Hunter Sung...
even get to the island?
[gasps]
Oh, there you are,
and just in time.
But how the hell did you...
I can explain it later.
Let's take care
of your wounds in the meantime.
Here, this should help.
Huh?
[JINWOO] Right. The system
won't let me hand these off.
You summoned that?
Your magic sure is handy.
Hunter Ma.
I need you to open your mouth.
Aah!
[gulps]
[gasps]
That's unreal.
[BAEK]
I'm healed.
Completely.
[groaning]
[coughs]
She's still in bad shape.
Why isn't it working?
[JINWOO]
Damn, just like before,
these can't work
when your health is too low.
And her aura is getting weaker.
Her wounds are too severe
for potions to heal.
We have to leave now.
I can clear a path for us.
-All right.
-[BAEK] Hold on!
-Huh?
[ants chirping]
They certainly swarm like
the bugs they are.
How are we gonna
take down so many of them?
[scoffs]
[door rattles]
[ASSOCIATE 24D, 24A]
Chairman Go!
Any news on the strike team?
[ASSOCIATE 24E]
No. Not yet.
Something's jamming
all comms from the island,
but hopefully
it's only temporary.
[ASSOCIATE 24A]
We can't get through
to Japanese command either.
Not sure why.
[ASSOCIATE 24D] Touched base
with the civilian media,
though, and the last thing
they saw was the black ant.
It's imperative
we get that signal back.
And I want those medic
and retrieval teams
ready to move out.
[HUNTER'S ASSOCIATION]
Yes, sir!
[indistinct chatter]
[door rattles shut]
[GUNHEE]
You know, Jinchul.
This has to be the most
I've ever resented
this aging body of mine.
Even if I'd be
of no help to them,
I wish I could join the fight.
Chairman Go.
Instead...
all I can do is pray.
♪
[thumping]
[JINAH] [grunting]
Stupid technology!
First the feed cuts
then the whole dang TV decides
this is the perfect time
to break!
We're jinxed!
Well, beating it up
won't fix it, honey.
[JINAH] [sighs]
Whatever.
I'll watch it in my room.
Bet my phone
will have updates!
Maybe.
[sighs]
That girl is so restless.
[SHIGEO]
I want answers, so explain.
Goto-san's vital signs
went silent, sir.
Right before
the signal was cut.
He was confronted
by a powerful enemy,
and likely killed.
[SHIGEO]
And the others?
We haven't verified.
[SHIGEO]
Well, figure it out!
Any further losses
will cost us in the next phase.
[REIJI]
On it.
[phone beeps]
[thuds]
[SHIGEO]
Goto got himself killed?
Useless moron.
What in the hell
is happening on that island?
[growls]
[roaring]
[wind gusting]
[all gasp]
[JINWOO] Elites like Igris
and Iron are holding their own.
But the foot soldiers
aren't doing so hot.
Part of me wants
to boost their numbers.
I just wish that
I didn't have an audience.
♪
-New plan.
-[ALL] Hm?
We're not making any progress.
Time to try a more
aggressive strategy.
See that mage?
You all hang back
and stay behind him.
My other shadows
will deal with the ant problem.
If any of 'em do get
past my soldiers,
make them regret it.
Easy enough.
We can handle a plan like that.
For sure!
[JINWOO]
One last thing.
Please keep what you're about
to see to yourselves.
Uh. Is he?
[exhales]
[ants buzzing]
[wind gusting]
[all gasp]
[wind whooshing]
♪
It came back already?
I thought it went after Goto.
Does that mean he lost?
♪
[loud screeching]
-[gasps]
-[wind gusting]
♪
[ANT KING]
There was no king outside.
Is he in here?
The one you call king?
♪
[JINWOO] I can't sense
the shadow I sent with Goto.
Now, I know why.
-Uh!
-Wait!
♪
[ANT KING]
Is it you?
Are you the king of humans?
Cute.
They got bugs
that can talk now.
[ANT KING]
Human.
Quite the remarkable aura.
Huh?
[loud roaring]
Okay.
But, you're still just a bug.
This might be
too much even for him!
I guess we're about to see.
-[grunting]
-[camera chimes]
Uh?!
[laughs]
[STAFF 24A] Director!
The feed is up again!
Wha...
Isn't he the...
It doesn't matter!
Let's just air it!
Sir!
You realize we'll be
broadcasting without any delay!
If something happens live,
we've no way
to stop it getting out!
We already cut
the broadcast once.
Can't get any worse than that!
-Do it!
-Yes! Right!
[keys clanking]
[PRODUCER 23A] Our future,
the battle, everything.
Is riding on this man!
[JOOHEE]
I can't believe it!
Me neither.
He's really there!
♪
[JINAH]
No...
way.
[JINAH]
Jinwoo?
He said
he was just stepping out!
What the heck?
He better break this habit!
[rattles]
He made it there!
Thank you, Hunter Sung!
It's him all right.
But how'd he reach them?
Point is he did it,
I don't care how!
Let's put our faith in him!
♪
[wind whooshing]
[thwacks]
-[wind gusting]
-[rumbling]
[all groaning]
Why would a mage
type get that close to it?
He underestimated
that ant's power.
And got clobbered for it!
[ANT KING]
Weak.
You are no king.
[gasps]
♪
[scoffs]
[spits]
[thwacks]
[wind gusting]
[rumbling]
♪
[DONGWOOK]
Um. Hey, guys.
Are you sure that
Hunter Sung is a mage?
I'm not sure about anything
when it comes to him.
And I definitely
didn't expect this.
[JINWOO]
He's pretty durable.
The exoskeleton maybe?
[thuds]
[growls softly]
[grunts]
[growls]
[battle grunts]
[rumbling]
[CAMERAMAN 22A]
Their punches are insane!
Even as an A-rank,
I can barely stay on my feet!
[thwacks]
I might pass out just
from the force of their magic!
[battle thuds]
[wind gusting]
[ANT KING]
Am I...being overpowered?
[thwacks]
[rumbling]
♪
How?
I do not understand.
How could a human
be so strong?
[thwacks]
[loud thud]
♪
[yelling]
[thwacks]
[groans]
-[heart pounding]
-[gasps]
[groans]
[JINWOO]
Poison?
[ANT KING] A mixture of toxins,
from the marine life here.
Its potency, amplified
by my magic power.
You will lose all ability
to move before long.
This is the end for you.
Die, human!
[laughs]
Seven KIA in a ten-man team?
Is that a joke?
[REIJI]
No. It's the facts.
We were able
to contact the three survivors,
and they confirmed it.
[groaning]
We lost over half our hunters?
This mission is a catastrophe!
Oh, and, we've also
detected a strong reading
near the island's caldera.
We think it's whatever
beat Goto-san, sir.
[SHIGEO] How is it alive
after fighting him?
And it's headed into the nest?
Why?
[REIJI]
No idea.
It could have some objective.
Or maybe it needs
a safe place to heal.
[gasps]
[SHIGEO] We don't know
if the Korean team is alive,
but if they are hanging
on by a thread,
Goto's killer will cut it.
They'll fall easily
in their state,
and the ants will be worn out
from fighting, too.
If we can strike down
the strong one,
the others will just be fodder.
[evil chuckle]
Victory is not lost!
Hurry up and recover
the three surviving S-ranks!
Once they've joined
the second strike team at sea,
send them back to the island!
[REIJI]
Those are your orders.
A chopper will be there soon.
Roger that.
♪
He wants to move ahead
with plan nine.
Let's go.
[HOSHINO]
It's hopeless.
That thing is a monster.
If we don't run,
then we're history.
[groans]
Get a grip!
No time for panic attacks!
Everyone who faced
that ant is dead!
All S-ranks!
And you wanna
volunteer to be next?
-[grunts]
-[groans]
[TAWATA]
You're pathetic.
We don't have any choice.
Deal with it.
[helicopter whirring]
♪
[growling]
[thwacks]
[bones cracking]
[screaming]
-[thuds]
-[rumbling]
Wait, I thought
he was just poisoned.
He seems okay,
but is he really?
[laughs]
At this point nothing
Hunter Sung does
will surprise me.
[JINWOO]
So, you had a secret weapon.
Ah, I was wondering
why you were holding
back earlier.
[system chimes]
[JINWOO] Maybe it's 'cause
my perception stat's
gotten so high.
But I can sense his emotions.
He's anxious.
That makes two of us.
Huh?
I can't waste any more time.
This ends now!
[thwacks]
[ant buzzing]
[ANT KING]
Poison is ineffective
and tests of strength
are pointless.
In that case...
♪
[wind whooshing]
[system chimes]
[sword clanks]
♪
[thuds]
[groaning]
[roars]
[electricity crackling]
-[battle grunts]
-[wind gusting]
[sword clanking]
[grunting]
[groans]
[swords clanking]
[battle grunts]
[roars]
[angry grunts]
[sword clanking]
-[rumbling]
-[panting]
[thudding]
♪
[ANT KING]
Speed that is equal to mine...
[thuds]
...and growing even faster.
[groans]
How is this possible?
♪
[all groan]
[electricity crackling]
[gasping]
[explosion]
[swords clanking]
[rumbling]
♪
[grunts]
[both grunting]
[swords clanking]
[roaring]
[grunting]
-[wind gusting]
-[groans]
♪
[gasps]
[JINWOO]
Upgrade.
Mutilation.
[sword clanks]
[ANT KING]
What happened?
-[angry grunt]
-[sword clanking]
[ANT KING]
How?
♪
'Course you regenerate.
[ANT KING]
What was that?
-[cracks]
-[blasts]
What in the world was that?
[roaring]
[screeches]
[thuds]
[wind gusting]
[ANT KING]
How dare you, you human?
You filthy human!
[screaming]
[electricity crackling]
Boys, get 'em.
[wind gusting]
[roaring]
[battle cries]
[ants chirping]
♪
[explosion]
[big explosion]
[fire roaring]
[ANT KING] But...
I was born to be
the absolute strongest being.
I devour all,
growing more powerful
with each enemy I consume.
I am supposed to be king.
I am supposed to...
[fire crackling]
Run away.
I must run away!
In order to survive,
I need to run away!
[whooshes]
[ANT KING]
Get as far as possible!
[thuds]
[screams]
♪
[screeching]
[ANT KING]
Hurry! Hurry!
Hurry and escape!
♪
[swords clanking]
[thudding]
♪
[system chiming]
[ants buzzing]
They're running scared.
Can't say I blame them.
Did we just win?
♪
[exhales]
[BAEK]
Hunter Sung!
♪
[whimpering]
[JINWOO]
Her aura's fading.
We don't have much time
We have to get her to a doctor!
There should be
a recovery helicopter
right outside!
-If we go now!
-No.
She won't
she'll last that long.
So we stay?
Thought your potions
were useless on her.
I haven't tried this one.
[hard breaths]
[gulps]
[JINWOO] The Elixir of Life
even cured Mom's Eternal Sleep.
This is, this is our last hope!
-[chimes]
-Huh?
No, no.
[DONGWOOK]
Did it not work?
[JINWOO] I can't leave
the island fast enough.
I can't use potions.
I can't use Shadow Exchange
because of the cooldown time!
So what?
What?
What the hell can I do?
♪
[ANT KING]
[unintelligible]